Hello, okay, so this is the time for you, let's
talk about some call and one more stock,
after that we will start the four of four. Bank
Nifty is currently showing a back swing for
you. ICICI Bank is on the lower side. Let's take
this and take a look at the
ICICI Bank rate on the screen once. 892 in this. Now this month,
actually ICICI Bank has consistently
underperformed, declining by around 6.5%.
This year,
ICICI Bank has been the biggest contributor to Nifty. There has been a six percent
decline this month, despite that,
if you look at the contribution of Nifty this year,
ICICI Bank has given the highest contribution.
Manas, where will this ICICI Bank be bought?
Look, I think that when you have Axis
Bank or other private banks or
PSU banks available
in the market, then it would be better to leave ICICI Bank for this time.
One reason for this is
that the stock is not sustaining above 20 and 50 moving averages, so
until
it reaches 815  I think you shouldn't buy here until it crosses 920. You should
n't buy on decline either. If
it slips below 880 and
closes below that, the decline
could increase. Because we're
talking about the short term,
what's the structure for the short term? That's why I was saying
not to buy on this decline
and let it continue, only then buy. Not at this time. There's
no confidence in the bank. Manas, by the way, some
action has started coming in Kotak as well. We will see that
too in the future. But for now, it's the turn of the four-way four
and all our experts are
ready today with all our
[sangeet].
Manas, you will give the
first train. For the cheapest option, you should pay
attention to Indian Hotel.
If you look at Indian Hotel, we
saw on Monday that the stock had given four boundaries at the lower level,
but after that, in the three consecutive days,
Indian Hotel has become a resistance
average. This means that if there is a
rally from here, you will see at least up to 340.
Therefore,
buy the call option of
Indian Hotel. Indian Hotel.  The
call option of 320 which is being traded at ₹10,
buy it there, it is
offering ₹1085, so buy it there,
stoppage of ₹8 will be purchased with a target of ₹17,
ok Indian Hotel's 320 call is
trading at 1085% and